KERMIT: Hi ho.
KERMIT：こんにちはホ。
Kermit the frog here, and this is a mystery box.
カーミットここカエル、これはミステリーボックスです。
You see, if anybody can guess from the clues I give what is
誰もが私が何であるかを与える手がかりから推測できる場合は、参照してください。
in this box, then they can keep what is in the box.
このボックスに、それらはボックス内にあるものを維持することができます。
COOKIE MONSTER: Is it cookie?
クッキーモンスター：それはCookieですか？
KERMIT: No, it is not a cookie.
KERMIT：いいえ、それはクッキーではありません。
COOKIE MONSTER: Bye bye.
クッキーモンスター：バイバイ。
KERMIT: But wait a second, Cookie Monster.
KERMIT：しかし、第二、クッキーモンスターを待ちます。
COOKIE MONSTER: What?
クッキーモンスター：何？
KERMIT: There are clues.
KERMIT：手がかりがあります。
COOKIE MONSTER: Who care about clues without cookie?
クッキーモンスター：クッキーなしで手がかりを気に？
Me want cookie.
私はクッキーをしたいです。
No cookie, no guessing game from clues.
クッキーは、何の手がかりからゲームを推測しません。
Arrivederci, Frog.
さようなら、カエル。
KERMIT: But wait a second, Cookie Monster.
KERMIT：しかし、第二、クッキーモンスターを待ちます。
Come back here.
ここに戻って。
You see, I'll tell you what I'll do.
あなたは私がやる何を教えてあげましょう、参照してください。
If you guess what is in the box, I'll give you a cookie.
あなたはボックス内にあるかを推測した場合、私はあなたにクッキーを与えるでしょう。
COOKIE MONSTER: It's a horse, it's a cow, it's a cotton
クッキーモンスター：それは、それは牛、馬のだ、それは綿です
ball, it's a pogo stick, it's a rump roast.
ボール、それは臀部ローストだ、ポゴスティックです。
KERMIT: No, no, no, no.
KERMIT：いや、いや、いや、いや。
COOKIE MONSTER: It's a moose.
クッキーモンスター：それはムースです。
Those are wild guesses.
これらは野生の推測です。
COOKIE MONSTER: Well, me wild about cookies.
クッキーモンスター：まあ、私のクッキーについての野生。
KERMIT: Yes, but you haven't guessed right.
KERMIT：はい、しかし、あなたは右推測していません。
Now, maybe if you listen to the clues.
さて、多分あなたは手がかりに耳を傾ける場合。
COOKIE MONSTER: OK, me all ears.
クッキーモンスター：OK、私のすべての耳。
OK, what's first clue?
[OK]を、最初の手がかりは何ですか？
KERMIT: OK, the first clue is that it is something to eat.
KERMIT：OK、最初の手がかりは、何か食べるものであるということです。
COOKIE MONSTER: It's a cookie.
クッキーモンスター：それはクッキーです。
KERMIT: No, it's not a cookie.
KERMIT：いいえ、それはクッキーではありません。
COOKIE MONSTER: Not a cookie.
クッキーモンスター：ないクッキー。
Give me second clue.
私の第二の手掛かりを与えます。
KERMIT: The second clue is that it is something round.
KERMIT：第二の手がかりは、それが何かのラウンドであるということです。
COOKIE MONSTER: A cookie.
クッキーモンスター：クッキー。
KERMIT: No, it's not a cookie.
KERMIT：いいえ、それはクッキーではありません。
COOKIE MONSTER: Not a cookie.
クッキーモンスター：ないクッキー。
KERMIT: Mm-mm.
KERMIT：MM-ミリメートル。
COOKIE MONSTER: Sorry, third clue.
クッキーモンスター：申し訳ありませんが、第三の手がかり。
KERMIT: Third clue.
KERMIT：サード手掛かり。
COOKIE MONSTER: Just thought it might be cookie off chance.
クッキーモンスター：ちょうどそれがチャンスをオフにクッキーかもしれないと思いました。
KERMIT: No, it's not.
KERMIT：いいえ、それはありません。
The color of this thing is orange.
この実物の色がオレンジ色です。
COOKIE MONSTER: Something to eat that is round and orange.
クッキーモンスター：それを食べるために何かが丸いとオレンジです。
It's a cookie.
これは、クッキーです。
KERMIT: (YELLING) No, it is not a cookie!
KERMIT：（叫ぶ）いいえ、それはクッキーではありません！
COOKIE MONSTER: Just thought one last chance, you know?
クッキーモンスターは：ちょうどあなたが知っている、最後のチャンスと思いましたか？
KERMIT: No, it's not a cookie.
KERMIT：いいえ、それはクッキーではありません。
COOKIE MONSTER: OK, um, me give up.
クッキーモンスター：OK、ええと、私はあきらめます。
KERMIT: What?
KERMIT：何？
How can you give up?
あなたはどのようにあきらめることができますか？
It's something to eat that's round and orange.
それはそれは、ラウンドとオレンジだ何か食べるものです。
It's an orange.
それはオレンジ色です。
It's an orange!
それはオレンジ色です！
COOKIE MONSTER: Me like that fourth clue.
クッキーモンスター：私その四手掛かりのような。
Is it an orange?
それはオレンジ色ですか？
KERMIT: (YELLING) Of course it's an orange.
KERMIT：もちろん、それはオレンジ色です（叫びます）。
I just told you it was an orange.
私はちょうどそれがオレンジ色だったことを言いました。
COOKIE MONSTER: Me guess right.
クッキーモンスター：私は正しいと思います。
Me get cookie.
私はクッキーを取得します。
Give me cookie.
私にクッキーを与えます。
KERMIT: No, you don't get a cookie.
KERMIT：いいえ、あなたはクッキーを得ることはありません。
COOKIE MONSTER: Why?
クッキーモンスター：なぜ？
KERMIT: I told you what it was.
KERMIT：私はそれが何であったかを語りました。
I told you it was an orange.
私はそれがオレンジ色だったことを言いました。
You didn't guess it right.
あなたはそれが正しいと思いませんでした。
COOKIE MONSTER: Frog.
クッキーモンスター：カエル。
KERMIT: What?
KERMIT：何？
COOKIE MONSTER: You know life, life not all
クッキーモンスター：あなたは人生を知って、人生ではないすべての
guessing games, frog.
推測ゲーム、カエル。
Sometimes, we have to care about the friends, especially
時には、私たちは特に、友人を気にする必要があります
friends who love cookies, friends who love cookies so
クッキーを愛する友人なので、クッキーを愛する友人
much they play silly guessing games because maybe, maybe
多くの彼らは多分、なぜなら多分愚かな推測ゲームをプレイ
just maybe a frog, a very handsome frog who has cookie
もしかしたらカエル、クッキーを持っている非常にハンサムなカエル
will give best, best friend who no can live without
なしなしでは生きことができる最高の、最高の友人を与えます
cookies, give that best friend a cookie.
クッキーは、その親友にクッキーを与えます。
But if friendship mean nothing--
しかし、友情はnothing--意味場合
KERMIT: OK.
KERMIT：OK。
OK, OK.
はいはい。
Here's your cookie.
ここにあなたのクッキーです。
COOKIE MONSTER: One measly cookie?
クッキーモンスター：Oneちっぽけなクッキー？
Speech like that deserves at least five cookies.
そのようなスピーチは、少なくとも5つのクッキーに値します。
KERMIT: I only had one cookie.
KERMIT：私は一つだけのクッキーを持っていました。
COOKIE MONSTER: OK.
クッキーモンスター：OK。
In that case, me settle.
その場合、私は落ち着きます。
[EATS COOKIE NOISILY]
【EATS COOKIEバタバタ]